Flowers in the Attic is a drama, mystery,
thriller film directed by Deborah Chow.
After the sudden death of their father, four children face
cruel treatment from their ruthless grandmother.
Corrine, played by Heather Graham.
Cathy, played by Kiernan Shipka.
Christopher, played by Mason Dye.
Carrie, played by Ava Telek.
Cory, played by Maxwell Kovach.
Bart, played by Dylan Bruce.
Flowers in the Attic is a 2014 Lifetime psychological
thriller drama movie directed by Deborah Chow.
It is the second adaptation of V.
Andrews’ 1979 novel of the same name.
A sequel, Petals on the Wind, based on the novel of the same
name, premiered on May 26, 2014, on Lifetime.
The network announced the developing of the following books in the series, If
There Be Thorns and Seeds of Yesterday, which both aired in 2015.
The film explores themes of sadistic,
grandfather, mansion, captive, molestation.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.